So now that we've practiced that, what I want you to do now is go ahead and do the same
thing.
I want you to autofocus any field you want on the new dish form that we have here.
So what I'm doing right here is just I sort of went ahead and did a little bit of
the migration over the script setups and you all have seen me do that a few times.
So if you're not need to walk you all through that whole thing.
So basically we have here the new dish form.
Did you all do okay as far as getting everything autofocus when you want it to?
Great.
This is good.
So let's run through this then.
So once again just like we talked about the first thing you want to do is decide which element
will be referenced.
So in this case I'll just pick this one.
So we can element call it dish name input and speed a bit more specific.
And then we define our ref.
So cons element dish name input.
This is a ref that could be an HTML input element or null.
And it will start out as null because when the page loads we don't know what it will be.
Then on mounted when the page has been loaded.
We will go ahead and say hey look if dish name input dot value exists with the question mark.
Then we'll go ahead and focus on it.
So just make sure that all this works as expected.
We go over here to dishes now and new.
There you go.
Name automatically shows up.